this with
the public education council, which ended with
the National Audit Office's review has one
game behind the scenes like me one day
will tell you but not really
than for people have not really disappeared
from their habits and can get hurt without it
I tell everything but uh a lot of it
we did then lead up to
could save this with
capitalization they were hiding behind
chapter eleven to avoid getting eh eh
pay the invoices or the receivables
which then several companies had thus received
confirmed by kronoford so that they therefore
it was just about buying time etc
eh and Peter Karlsson already says that